nfhslearn.com 2019-12-14

# NFHS Learn | Interscholastic Education, Made Easy

### Privacy Policy

  * **Privacy Policy/Your Privacy Rights**

Effective: 8/1/2012

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which the National Federation of State High School Associations (“NFHS”), an Illinois not-for-profit corporation, collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of its www.nfhs.org and www.nfhslearn.com websites and any derivative or affiliated websites on which this Privacy Policy is posted (collectively, the “Website”). NFHS reserves the right, at its discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time by posting such changes to this page. You understand that you have the affirmative obligation to check this Privacy Policy periodically for changes, and you hereby agree to periodically review this Privacy Policy for such changes. The continued use of the Website following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy constitutes an acceptance of those changes.

  * **Privacy**

NFHS is committed to safeguarding the information Users entrust to NFHS and believes that every User should know how it utilizes the information collected from Users. The Website is not directed at children under 13 years of age, and NFHS does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 years of age online. Please note that the Website may contain links to other websites. These linked sites may not be operated or controlled by NFHS. NFHS is not responsible for the privacy practices of these or any other websites, and you access these websites entirely at your own risk. NFHS recommends that you review the privacy practices of any other websites that you choose to visit. 

NFHS is based, and this Website is hosted, in the United States of America. If User is from the European Union or other regions of the world with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law and User is visiting, accessing or otherwise using the Website, please note that any personally identifiable information that User provides to NFHS will be transferred to the United States. Any such personally identifiable information provided will be processed and stored in the United States by NFHS or a service provider acting on its behalf. By providing personally identifiable information to NFHS, User hereby specifically and expressly consents to such transfer and processing and the uses and disclosures set forth herein. 

  * **The Information NFHS Collects**

NFHS may collect personally identifiable information from Users in a variety of ways. Personally identifiable information may include, without limitation, (i) contact data (such as a User’s name, mailing and email addresses); (ii) demographic data; and (iii) other information requested during any account registration process or through any functionality on the Website. If a User communicates with NFHS by email or otherwise, posts messages to any forums, completes online forms, surveys or entries or otherwise interacts with or uses the features on the Website, any information provided in such communications may be collected by NFHS. NFHS may also collect information about how Users use the Website, for example, by tracking the number of unique views received by the pages of the Website, or the domains and IP addresses from which Users originate. While not all of the information that NFHS collects from Users is personally identifiable, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that Users provide NFHS through the Website or otherwise. 

NFHS may use “cookies” or “web beacons” to track how Users use the Website. A cookie is a piece of software that a web server can store on Users’ PC or other device and use to identify Users should they visit the Website again. Users may adjust their web browser software if they do not wish to accept cookies. 

    1. **How NFHS Uses Information**

NFHS may use personally identifiable information collected through the Website for the specific purposes for which the information was collected, to contact Users regarding products and services offered by NFHS and other related companies and its trusted affiliates, 

independent contractors and business partners, and otherwise to enhance Users’ experience with NFHS and such affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. NFHS may also use information collected through the Website for research regarding the effectiveness of the Website and the business planning, marketing, advertising and sales efforts of NFHS and other related companies, its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. 

    2. **Disclosure of Information**

NFHS may disclose personally identifiable information collected from Users to other related companies, trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners who will use the information for the purposes outlined above, as necessary to provide the services offered by the Website and the Website itself, and the specific purposes for which the information was collected. NFHS may disclose personally identifiable information at the request of law enforcement or governmental agencies or in response to subpoenas, court orders or other legal process, to establish, protect or exercise NFHS’s legal or other rights or to defend against a legal claim or as otherwise required by law. NFHS may disclose personally identifiable information in order to protect the rights, property or safety of a User or any other person. NFHS may disclose personally identifiable information to investigate or prevent a violation by User of any contractual or other relationship with NFHS or the perpetration of any illegal or harmful activity. NFHS may also disclose aggregate, anonymous data based on information collected from Users to investors and potential partners. Finally, NFHS may disclose or transfer personally identifiable information collected from Users in connection with or in contemplation of a sale of its assets or business or a merger, consolidation or other reorganization of its business.

    3. **Security of Information**

Information about Users that is maintained on NFHS’s systems is protected using industry standard security measures. However, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable, and NFHS cannot guarantee that the information submitted to, maintained on or transmitted from its systems will be completely secure. NFHS is not responsible for the circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures relating to the Website by any Users or third parties.

  * **Correcting, Updating, Accessing or Removing Personal Information**

If a User’s personally identifiable information changes, or if a User no longer desires to receive non-account specific information from NFHS, NFHS will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update and/or remove that User’s previously-provided personal data. This can be done by emailing a request to NFHS via the NFHS Contact Us page. Additionally, you may request access to the personally identifiable information as collected by NFHS by sending a request to NFHS as set forth above. Please note that in certain circumstances, NFHS may not be able to completely remove a User’s information from its systems. For example, NFHS may retain a User’s personal information for legitimate business purposes, if it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, for account recovery purposes, if required by law or as retained in NFHS data backup systems or cached or archived pages. All retained personally identifiable information will continue to be subject to the terms of the Privacy Policy to which the User has previously agreed.

  * **Contacting NFHS**

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, you may contact NFHS via the contact form on the NFHS website: http://www.nfhs.org/ContactUs.aspx
